[Music]
if
together we will pull each other
oh good morning keo it's early did you
Sleet well
shut up we're running late hurry up and
get dressed so we can go downstairs for
breakfast
i need my apple and cinnamon oatmeal
because there's a big test at school
this afternoon
okay i'll hurry up then sorry
hey keo why do we have to Sleet in the
same bed
i mean can tell man full poor ray don't
do that
you want to know why i'll tell you why
zach
it's because I am dedicated dedicated to
win this battle
and make you the mom out oaking it
strengthens our bond and [ __ ]
okay but why do you touch my butt
your questions will all be answered in
due time's edge
just get dressed zuch what the [ __ ] are
you wearing
i thought I told you to Sleet but naked
i didn't want to
i felt uncomfortable uncomfortable
such that is a feeling you will someday
have to overcome
what does that mean keo I don't
understand what the [ __ ] any of this
means
I'm like six years old [ __ ] if you try
touching my ass
I'm calling the cops again whatever i
wasn't trying to do anything anyways
you're wasting time at this point I'm
gonna go poop
damn I forgot we are out of toilet paper
hey zach I'm gonna use a bit of paper
from your spell book is that okay
like hell put the book down now partners
aren't supposed to wipe their stinky ass
with their
mamoka spell books yeah well I'm doing
it anyway
hey keo don't talk to me can't you see
I'm taking a [ __ ]
and move over I can't see the tv
but keo I need your help okay
fine what do you want it's vulcan 300
i can't find him anywhere I was hoping
you might know where he is
no I don't have a clue sorry oh
wait never mind you I know where he is
i used him to wipe my butt crack you
can't find him in the garbage can
what in the world volkman 300 he's
he's covered and went crap damn you damn
you kill takamine
i won't let you keep getting away with
this shut up and make my oatmeal
what the [ __ ] is that [ __ ] that's not
the usual fruit box
keo what kind of shitty ass bootleg
design is this
i want the real fruit loops not this
wannabe piece of trash
it's just a drawings etch calm down and
eat your cereal
it's a step backwards and art and
evolution that's what I say
put Sonic Underground on tv I need to
see some real art to get that pile of
poop out of my mind
triplets born the throne
as serious of untouched faith
hello this is the takamine residence how
can I help you
no oh no please you can't be serious
yes I understand I will let zach know
he's having breakfast right now but i
will tell him
keo did something happen isn't the moto
attacking the city
such you might want to sit down for this
concho may
he he's in the hospital
[Music]
you